신혼여행 때문에 설레지?
Aren't you excited we're going
on our honeymoon?
맞아
Yeah, I am.
딴 사람 오기 전에 실컷 불러
That's right, get it out of your system
while we're alone.
- 인사하러 왔어
- 신혼여행 잘 다녀와
-Hey. We came to say goodbye.
-Yeah. Have a great honeymoon.
- 고마워
- 난 채비를 해야겠어
-Thanks.
-I better go pack.
내가 벌써 짐을 쌌어
네 스피도 수영복만 빼고
No, I already packed. The only thing
I couldn't find, though, was your Speedo.
스피도?
난 그런 수영복이 없는데
Speedo? I don't have a Speedo.
난 가서 긴 수영복을
챙겨 놓을게
I'm gonna go pack my regular,
long bathing suit.
아직 안 갔구나
신혼여행 잘 갔다와
Good, you're still here! I wanted
to tell you to have a good honeymoon.
고마워!
Thank you!
오늘 애 아빠에게
임신사실을 알릴 거야
And I also wanted you guys to know
that I am telling the father today.
왜들 이래?
What? What?
- 아빠는 로스잖아
- 어떻게 알았어?
-We know it's Ross.
-How? How do you know?
그 스웨터의 주인이
바로 로스야
It was his sweater. But, oh, my God!
너희들도 알고 있다니
마음이 놓인다
I so wanted Ross to know first.
But I am so relieved that you guys know!
난 아기의 이모가 되겠군
That is so great. And I'm gonna be
your baby's aunt!
그러게 말야
I know.
나도
Me too!
난 삼촌이 되는 거야
And I'm gonna be an uncle! Come here.
- 다들 이모, 삼촌들이지
- 내가 유일한 혈육이군
-You're all gonna be aunts and uncles.
-Yeah, but I'm the only one related by blood.
로스에게 어떻게 말하면 좋을지
너희가 충고해 줘
So now that you all know, you can help me.
Give me some advice on how to tell Ross.
네 계획은?
What were you gonna say?
난 아이를 낳을 테니까
알아서 결정하라고
I was gonna tell him that I'm gonna have it,
and he can be as involved as he wants.
괜찮게 들리는데
Well, that sounds good.
어떤 말로 말문을
열어야 좋을까?
Yeah, but, you know, how do I start?
I mean, what's the first thing that I say?
- 알았어, 고마워
- 행운을 빌어
-Okay, great. Thanks.
-Hey, good luck.
안녕
Yeah, bye.
무슨 일이야?
Hey, what was that all about?
레이첼과 로스가
아이의 부모가 될 거야
Guess there's no harm in telling you now.
Rachel and Ross are going to have a baby.
뭐라고? 그런 일을
왜 나만 모르고 있었지?
What?! I didn't even know that..!
Why didn't you tell me?
내가 왜 이러지?
Why am I talking like this?
- 넌 입이 가벼우니까
- 뭐?
-I didn't think you could keep it a secret.
-What?!
뭐?
What?!
난 비밀 얘기를 퍼뜨린 적이
한 번도 없단 말야
I am an excellent secret-keeper.
I have kept all our secrets.
- 무슨 비밀?
- 안 돼, 조이
-What secrets?
-No, no, Joey.
난 입이 무겁기 때문에
절대 말할 수 없어
I'm not gonna tell you, because
I am an excellent secret-keeper.
- 나중에 알려줄 거지?
- 너도 벌써 아는 얘기야
-You'll tell me later?
-You already know.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'로스의 아이'
신혼여행을 보내는 일은
정말 낭만적이야
It's so romantic to send people off
on their honeymoon.
모니카와 챈들러는 결혼했고
로스와 레이첼은 아기를 가졌잖아
You know, Monica and Chandler are
married. Ross and Rachel are having a baby.
- 우리도 뭔가 해야겠어
- 때가 되면 그때 하자
-Maybe you and I should do something.
-All in good time, my love. All in good time.
기타를 아파트에 두고 왔어
나중에 열어줄 거지?
Shoot! I left my guitar in their apartment.
Well, you can let me in later, right?
걔들이 내 열쇠를 가졌어
No, I don't have a key.
They took mine to give to you.
- 내 열쇠도 가져갔는데
- 뭐 때문에 열쇠를 가져갔지?
-What? They took mine to give to you.
-Why would they take away our keys?
우리를 못 믿나 봐
Maybe they don't trust us.
저번엔 내게 열쇠를 맡겼다고
They let me keep my key the last time
they were out of town.
케찹병을 깨고
모니카의 수건으로 닦았을 때?
The time you broke the ketchup bottle
and cleaned it with Monica's guest towels?
- 수건은 빨았어
- 네가 언제?
-Hey, I washed those.
-No, you didn't.
맞아, 내가 그랬을 리 없지
Yeah, that didn't sound like me.
- 기타를 써야하는데 어쩌지?
- 그 집에 내 물건도 있어
-What will I do? I really need my guitar.
-I have stuff in there too.
- 무슨 물건?
- 모니카의 치킨 파르마
-What stuff?
-Monica's chicken parm. I'll take care of it.
트리거 씨, 조이입니다
Hey, Mr. Treeger? It's Joey Tribbiani.
제가 모니카와 챈들러의 집에
들어가야 하거든요
Listen, I need to get into Monica and
Chandler's apartment. It's an emergency!
가스가 새고 있어요
마늘빵도 가져오세요
Gas leak. Oh, and bring garlic bread.
- 벌써 출발했어?
- 응
-Hey, did Monica and Chandler take off yet?
-Yeah.
이런, 박물관의 출입증을
안 가져갔잖아
Damn. They left without my pass to the
Nassau Fossil and Natural History Museum.
신혼여행을 망쳤군
There goes the honeymoon.
- 레이첼과 만났어?
- 아니, 왜?
-Did Rachel find you?
-No, why?
널 찾던데
She was looking for you.
나중에 만나야겠군
Well, I guess I'll catch up
with her later.
- 급한 일이라던데
- 중요한 일 같았어
-She really wanted to talk to you now.
-Yeah, it seemed pretty important.
이런
Oh, no.
뭐?
What?
무슨 일인지 짐작이 가
I think I might know what this is about.
정말?
Really?
아무에게도 말하지 말자고
서로 약속했는데...
Yeah. We promised we weren't
gonna tell anybody this, but..
한 달 전, 내가
레이첼과 같이 잤어
About a month ago,
Rachel and I slept together.
그리고?
And?
네가 훨씬 놀랄 줄 알았는데
Wow, I thought you'd be
a little more shocked.
미안, 그리고?
Oh, sorry. And?!
당시엔 실수라고 생각했는데
Well, we said we'd just do it
that one time..
레이첼도 만남을 유지하고
싶어하는 것 같아
but now I think she may wanna
start things up again.
내가 보기엔 그렇지 않아
Yeah, I don't think that's what it is.
- 어째서? 그럼?
- 몸이 안 좋군
-Why? What else could it be?
-Oh, wow, I don't feel well.
내 예상이 틀림없다니까
I'm telling you, that's what it is.
결혼식에서도 레이첼이 날
이상한 눈으로 쳐다봤어
No wonder she was looking at me
all funny during the wedding.
너희는 들은 얘기 없어?
She didn't say anything to you?
- 뭘 잘못 먹었군
- 맞아
-Maybe it's something you ate.
-Could be, yeah.
- 레이첼에게 직접 물어봐
- 맞아, 그래야겠어
-Please, just go and talk to Rachel.
-Yeah, I guess I should.
내가 짚이는 게 있어
Man, you know what I have to realize?
난 하룻밤만 지낼 남자가
아니란 생각이 들어
Maybe I'm not the type of guy
women can have just one night with.
항상 여자들이 무언가를
더 원하거든
You know, they always seem
to want a little bit more.
언제나 유념해야겠어
I should remember that.
다음 분
Next.
- 우리가 먼저 가자
- 사랑에 빠졌으니 놔두자
-They're kissing. Let's just go around them.
-Leave them alone. They're in love.
나도 사랑에 빠졌지만
차례는 지켜야지
I'm in love too. But in an orderly fashion.
다음 분
Next.
걸으면서 할 순 없나요?
다음 분을 불러요
Hi. Can you do that and walk?
Because she said, "Next."
죄송해요, 못 들었어요
신혼여행이거든요
Sorry, we didn't hear you.
We're on our honeymoon.
뭔가 해 드려야겠군요
1등석에 빈자리가 없어요
Let me see what I can do.
There are some first-class seats available.
신혼여행이라니까
1등석으로 옮겨 줬어
They bumped them up to first class
because they're on their honeymoon!
- 우리도 신혼부부 행세를 하자
- 신혼부부 맞잖아
-Let's act like we're on our honeymoon.
-We are on our honeymoon.
내 엉덩이를 잡아
Grab my ass.
- 다음 분
- 못 들을 뻔했어요
-Next.
-Hi. Sorry, I almost didn't hear you.
제가 새 남편에게 빠졌거든요
신혼여행 중이에요
You know, I'm just so in love with my new
husband. We're on our honeymoon.
- 결혼을 축하합니다
- 감사합니다
-Congratulations.
-Thanks.
빙 씨는 25J,
빙 부인은 25K입니다
Okay, Mr. Bing, you'll be in 25J,
and Mrs. Bing, you're in 25K.
신혼여행 가는 길인데
1등석으로 옮기면 안 돼요?
We're on our honeymoon, so can you do
your little thing and bump us to first class?
저 부부가 옮긴 자리가
마지막 두 좌석이었어요
I'm sorry, all the first-class seats are taken.
That couple got the last two.
아까 먼저 왔으면
우리 자리였는데, 젠장!
See? If we'd gone around them like I said,
she'd have given us those tickets! Damn it!
25J와 25K는 확실히
붙어있겠죠?
25J and K, any chance
those aren't together?
열쇠를 가져가다니 너무해
넌 네 열쇠를 내게 맡기잖아
I still can't believe they took away my key.
I mean, you trust me with yours.
물론이지
Of course I do!
And I'm gonna get it back to you..
열쇠광택이 끝나는 대로
네게 줄게
just as soon as they're done with it
at the key-shining place.
- 무슨 일이지?
- 모르겠어
-What the hell is that?
-I don't know.
트리거 씨, 뭐 하세요?
Treeger, what are you doing?
- 가스가 샌다고 했잖아요
- 열쇠는 어떡하고요?
-You said there was a gas leak.
-Why not use your key?
열쇠를 찾는 동안
건물이 폭발할까 봐서요
By the time I found it on this thing,
the whole place might have exploded.
내 건물이 또 터지면
입장이 난처해지거든요
If that happens at another building
I manage, people will ask questions.
어서 서둘러요
Come on, hurry up!
저건 우리도 할 수 있는데
Well, we could have done that.
저기 봐, 1등석 라운지에
들어가고 있어
Look at that! They're going
into the first-class lounge.
- 안에 뭐가 있는 줄 알아?
- 아니
-Do you know what they have in there?
-No.
나도 몰라, 들어가 보자
Me neither. We have to get in!
- 태연하게 굴어
- 어머, 오렌지야!
-Just act like you belong.
-Oh, my God! Oranges!
- 또 만나서 반가워요
- 비행기표 좀 보여주세요
-Nice to see you again.
-Sir, may I see your tickets, please?
물론이죠
Yes, of course.
좌석란이 안 보여요
Would you move your thumb?
I can't see the seat number.
제가 외워서 괜찮아요
1A랍니다
That's all right.
I have it memorized. It's 1A.
- 죄송하지만, 1등석 표가 아니군요
- 죄송할 것 없습니다
-Sir, this isn't a first-class ticket. I'm sorry.
-Apology accepted. Excuse us.
죄송하지만 이곳에서
나가 주십시오
Sir, I'm afraid I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave.
알았어요
Fine.
어서 가자
Go, go!
- 안녕
- 어서 와
-Hi.
반가워
Hi.
우리 대화가 필요한 것 같아
I think there's something
that we really need to talk about.
나도 동감이야
들어가서 얘기하자
I think we do. Why don't we go inside.
- 무슨 일인지 알겠어
- 그래?
-Look, I know why you're here.
-You do?
응, 네가 창피하지 않도록
Yeah, and to save you
from any embarrassment..
내가 먼저 말할게
I think maybe I should talk first.
- 좋아
- 그래
-Okay.
-Okay?
로스와 레이첼
Ross and Rachel.
레이첼과 로스
Rachel and Ross.
그날은 정말 광란의 밤이었지?
That's been one heck of a seesaw,
hasn't it?
뭐?
What?
우리가 함께 보낸 밤 말야
재미있고 화끈했다고
I mean, look, that one night we had
was fun and certainly passionate.
하지만 친구로 남는 쪽이
좋을 것 같지 않아?
But don't you think it's better
if we just stay friends?
진짜 용건이 뭐야?
Seriously, what?
알았어
Okay. You know what?
네가 원한다면
한 번 더 할 수도 있어
If you want to,
we can do it one more time.
난 괜찮단 얘기야
그리고 지금도 한가해
I mean, I'd be okay with that.
In fact, I have some time right now..
됐어
Okay.
이제 말해도 되지?
You know what? Can I talk now?
- 그럼
- 좋아
-Oh, sure.
-Okay.
나 임신했어
I'm pregnant.
로스?
Ross?
너만 준비가 된다면
Okay, whenever you're ready.
네가 아기의 아빠야
And you're the father, by the way.
But you got..
- 물 좀 마실래?
- 난 괜찮아
-Can I get you some water?
-I'm good.
로스, 부담가지지 말고
네가 원하는 대로 해
Ross, there is no pressure on you, okay? I
mean, you can be as involved as you want.
난...
Yeah, I..
잘 모르겠어
이해가 안 돼
I'm just, I don't know.
I don't understand..
그게 가능할까?
how this happened.
- 콘돔을 착용했잖아
- 나도 알아
-We used a condom.
-I know.
하지만 콘돔의 안전성은
97%에 지나지 않아
But you know, condoms only work,
like, 97 percent of the time.
뭐?
What?
What?!
그럼, 콘돔갑에 명시해 둬야지
Well, they should put that on the box!
- 그렇게 나와 있어
- 아니야
-They do.
-No, they don't!
검정색으로 큼지막하게
써 놨어야지!
Well, they should put it
in huge block letters!
- 콘돔은 잊어버려
- 잊어버린 거나 다름없어
-Ross, let's just forget about the condoms.
-Well, I may as well have!
나도 임신사실을 알고
Listen, you know what?
I was really freaked out too..
- 미치는 줄 알았어
- 난 그런 감정이 아니야
-when I found out.
-Freaked..? Hey, I'm not freaked out.
소비자로서 분개한 거라고
I'm indignant as a consumer!
- 그냥 다음에 얘기하자
- 아냐, 지금 하고 싶어
-You know what? Let's talk later.
-No, I wanna talk now.
내 말은...
In fact, I wanna talk..
콘돔회사 사장과
대화를 나눠야겠어
to the president
of the condom company.
난 다음에 다시 올게
Okay, you know what?
Maybe I should come back.. Okay.
알았어, 1번을 누를게
Yeah, I'll press one!
- 가스가 새는 곳이 없어요
- 그럼 데워 먹어도 되죠?
-I looked everywhere. There's no gas leak.
-So then I can heat this up?
문을 새로 달아야겠어요
Anyway, I'll get moving
on that new door.
이 사실을 챈들러와 모니카에게
비밀로 해 주세요
Great. Listen, could you do us a favor and
not tell Chandler and Monica about this?
왜냐하면, 그 친구들은
자식이 없어서
Because, you know, they don't have
any kids of their own..
이 문을 자식처럼
생각했거든요
and this door was like a child to them.
자물쇠가 달라서
어차피 알게 돼 있어요
Well, I'm gonna have to put on a new lock.
They'll find out anyway.
하루종일 걸리는군
요가수업을 취소해야겠어
It's looking like an all-day job.
I'm gonna have to cancel my yoga class.
로스, 재스민에게
못 간다고 전해 줘요
Hey, Ross. Could you tell Jasmine
I can't make it to yoga class today?
물론이죠
Sure.
- 맙소사, 문이 왜 이래?
- 티가 나?
-Oh, my God! What happened to the door?
-So it's noticeable, huh?
- 레이첼 있어?
- 아직 얘기하지 않았어?
-Look, is Rachel here? I need to talk to her.
-Didn't you two already talk?
하긴 했는데...
Yeah, but..
내가 레이첼과 잔 사실은
너희도 알 테고
Okay. Look, you guys know
that Rachel and I slept together..
다른 일이 있어
but there's something else.
레이첼이 임신했어
Rachel's pregnant.
- 맙소사!
- 어떻게 그럴 수가!
-Holy mother of God!
-Oh, my God, I can't believe that!
- 내 아이야
- 난 금시초문이야
-With my child.
-That is brand-new information!
- 알고 있었구나?
- 대충
-You already know, don't you?
-Little bit.
- 좀 어때?
- 괜찮아, 아니, 괜찮아질 거야
-How you doing?
-Okay. I mean, I'll be okay.
내가 잘 대처하지 못했어
It's just, I don't think
I handled it very well.
- 뭐라고 했는데?
- 아무 말도 안 했어
-What'd you say to her?
-Nothing.
대신, 콘돔사의 고객부엔
귀에 박히도록 얘기했어
But the complaint department
at the condom company got an earful.
- 그러느라 레이첼을 놓쳤지
- 로스...
-Then when I turned around, she was gone.
-Oh, Ross.
콘돔의 안전성이 97%밖에
안 된단 사실도 알게 됐어
I know. But in my defense, I just found out
that condoms are only, like, 97% effective.
- 뭐?
- 레이첼을 찾아야 해
-What?
-I gotta go find her.
잠깐, 그게 사실이야?
Hey. Hold on! Are you serious?
그럼, 나머지 3%는
위험하단 소리야?
So, like, 3 percent of the time,
they don't even work?
콘돔갑에 써 놔야지!
They should put that on the box!
- 씌어 있어
- 그래?
-Evidently, they do.
-What?!
사실이군
Well, I'll be.
- 믿기지가 않아
- 말도 안 돼
-I can't believe we're here.
-You've gotta be kidding.
뭐?
What?
결혼선물로 허니문 스위트를
드리겠습니다
As a wedding gift to you, the hotel would
like to give you the honeymoon suite.
하루종일 우리를 방해하다니!
No! You have been screwing us all day!
- 누구시죠?
- 10초 늦은 당신들의 모습이에요
-Who are you?
-We're you. Just 10 seconds later!
댁들은 1등석을 얻었잖아요
우리도 뭐라도 받아야죠
You already got the first-class tickets,
the lounge. We should get free stuff too!
우리도 신혼부부라고요
You're not the only ones
on your honeymoon!
정 그렇다면 당신들이
허니문 스위트를 써요
You can have the suite if you want.
We don't care about where we stay.
우린 사랑을 축하하러 왔어요
We're here to celebrate our love
for each other.
함께 있기만 하면
다른 건 필요없죠
We don't have to get free stuff.
We just want to be together.
우린 필요해요
We need the stuff.
모니카, 나 조이야
너희 집에서 가스냄새가 나
Monica, it's Joey. Phoebe and I smell gas
coming from your apartment.
- 조이가 냄새가 난대
- 다른 일은 없어?
-What? Are you serious? Joey smells gas.
-What else is new?
- 너희가 우리 열쇠를 가져갔잖아
- 어떻게든 무슨 수를 써 봐
-We'd check it out, but you took our keys.
-Well, do something. Get in there!
- 문을 부수면 될 것 같아
- 그렇게 해
-How? I guess I could break down your door.
-Yeah, do that.
- 우리가 변상할 필요는 없지?
- 그럼
-And you won't blame us for any damage?
-No.
- 아무 소리도 안 나는데
- 내가 부술게
-Are you doing it? I don't hear anything.
-Okay, I'll break it down.
지금 조이가 대문을
부수고 있어
Hi. He's doing it,
he's breaking down the door.
방금 들어왔어
Okay, we're in.
- 편안하세요?
- 그렇다면 나쁘게 생각할 거죠?
-Okay, Rachel, are you comfortable?
-If I said I was, would you judge me?
선생님이 곧 오실 거예요
The doctor'll be here in a minute
to do your sonogram.
네
Okay.
가구점에서도 이런 걸 판다면
반드시...
Oh, man, I swear, if they sold these
at Pottery Barn..
- 안녕
- 반가워
-Hi.
얘기 좀 하자
We need to talk.
지금? 지금은 좀 곤란한데
Right now? Because I kind of got
an alfresco situation going on over here.
아침에 내가 한 행동에 대해
사과하고 싶어
Please, I really.. I want to apologize
for the way I acted earlier today.
- 괜찮아, 내 머리 쪽에 있어 줘
- 뭐? 응, 미안
-That's fine. Can you stay up near my head?
-What? Oh, yeah, sorry.
네 입장은 헤아리지 못하고
내 생각만 했나 봐
I went crazy. I was thinking about myself
when I should've been thinking about you..
- 로스, 머리 쪽으로!
- 알았어
-Okay, head, Ross! Head, Ross!
-Right.
네 곁에 있어줄 거란 걸
알아줬으면 해
I want you to know that I'm gonna be there
through this whole thing. Okay?
진찰, 분만수업...
아기 소변에 대한 방수까지 말야
The doctor's appointments, the Lamaze
classes, baby-proofing the apartment.
그건 결혼 후 걱정해
Although, we can worry about that
after we get married.
- 결혼?
- 결혼해야 되지 않을까?
-Married?
-Well, yeah, I think we should get married.
넌 툭하면 결혼 얘기야?
Because that's your answer to everything?
그게 바람직한 일이니까
No. Because that's the right thing to do.
그건 우리가 서로
사랑할 때의 얘기야
Yeah, maybe, if you're in love.
But Ross, we are not in love, are we?
그렇지만 너 혼자 이 일을
감당할 순 없잖아
No. But still, I mean,
you can't possibly do this alone.
뭐라고?
Excuse me?
- 식당에서 혼자 밥도 못 먹잖아
- 뭐?
-You can't even eat alone in a restaurant.
-What?
혼자 먹지도 못하는데
어떻게 혼자서 아기를 키우겠어?
If you can't eat by yourself, how do you
expect to have a baby by yourself?
- 나 혼자 먹을 수 있어!
- 네가 언제?
-I can too eat by myself!
-When have you ever?
어떤 사람이 먼저 일어났을 때!
When certain people leave the table
and I am not finished!
어떤 사람은 수프를 먹는데
2시간이나 걸리지!
Well, certain other people take two hours
to eat a bowl of soup!
넌 너무 빨리 먹어
Oh, please. You inhale your food.
I grew up with Monica.
If you didn't eat fast, you didn't eat!
난 모니카와 자라서
늦으면 빼앗겨 버린다고!
내가 방해했나요?
Am I interrupting?
롱 박사님, 들어오세요
애 아빠인 로스예요
No, Dr. Long. Please come in.
This is Ross. He is the father.
남편은 아니에요
혼자 감당할 수 있다는군요
But not the husband, because,
evidently, she can do this alone.
반갑습니다
그럼 시작하겠습니다
Nice to meet you. I'll get started on this.
- 왜 내가 필요하단 말을 못해?
- 내 머리 쪽에 필요해!
-Why you can't admit you need me?
-I need you to stay near my head!
모두 좋아 보이는군요
화면을 같이 보시죠
Okay. Everything looks good.
Here it is on the screen.
이 부분이 자궁이고
Here's your uterus..
태아는 여기 있습니다
and right here is your baby.
세상에
Oh, my God.
저기 있어, 아기가 보여
There it is. I see it.
축하합니다
자리를 비워 드릴게요
Congratulations.
I'll give you two a minute.
- 네
- 감사합니다
-Okay.
-Thank you.
정말 신기하지?
Pretty amazing, huh?
안 보여!
I don't see it!
- 뭐?
- 안 보인다고
-What?
-I can't see it.
방금 보인다며
But you just said that you did.
형편없는 엄마가 되기 싫어서
거짓말한 거야
I know. I lied. I didn't want her
to think I was a terrible mother.
자신의 아기도 못 보다니!
I can't even see my own baby!
이리 와, 너도 볼 수 있어
바로 여기 있잖아
Oh, sure. Come here. Sure, you can.
Come here. Look, it's right there.
예쁘구나
Oh, it's beautiful.
이제 보여
I see it now.
- 정말이야?
- 아니
-Do you really?
-No, I don't see it!
알았어, 이리 와 봐
Okay. Come on. All right. Okay.
땅콩처럼 생긴
조그마한 게 보여?
You see this tiny thing
that looks like a peanut?
응
Yeah.
바로 그거야
Sweetie, that's it.
그래?
That's it?
그건 아까 봤어
Well, I saw that.
- 고마워
- 고맙긴
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
저게 우리의 아기라니
믿기지가 않아
Wow, I can't believe that's our baby.
맞아, 우리의 아기야
Yeah, that's our baby.
문을 새로 달았어
Well, they put up the new door.
- 문단속은 확실한 거야?
- 응, 왜?
-So it's all locked up and secure?
-Yeah. Why?
모니카가 만든 파이가
먹고 싶어 미치겠거든
I was trying to figure out how bad
I want one of Monica's turkey pot pies.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
-Hi.
-Hey.
- 진찰은 어땠어?
- 모두 괜찮았어
-So how was the doctor?
-Everything went great.
- 잘됐네
- 네 자궁사진을 보여 줘
-Good.
-Hey, show them the picture of your uterus.
아기가 어디 있어?
I don't see the baby. Where is it?
나도 처음엔 못 찾았는데
아기는...
Oh, no, I know. I couldn't see it either
at first. But it's right..
로스, 또 잊어버렸어
Ross, I lost it again.